Indra Levi Manahan

indra.levi.manahan@gmail.com

+1(226) 899-9945

Phone:

352 Cooper Street, Cambridge, ON

N3C 3X8

SUMMARY

A customer-centric, creative person with demonstrated leadership skills. Has multiple years of experience managing and leading organizations in various roles. Maintains a strong working relationship with coworkers and clients to enhance efficiency, productivity, and job satisfaction. Excellent communication skills and problem-solving abilities.

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

Proficient in Javascript. Familiar with Ruby, Swift, C++, Python.

Web Development:

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Bulma, Handlebars, Vite
- Backend: Node.js, Express
- Responsive Design and Cross-Browser Compatibility

Database Management:

- MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB
- Database Design and Optimization

Version Control:

Git, GitHub, GitLab

Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC):

• Agile and Scrum Methodologies

Problem Solving:

- Analytical Thinking and Troubleshooting
- Algorithm Design and Optimization

Tools and Platforms:

Visual Studio Code, Heroku, Render, Netlify

Communication:

- Strong Verbal and Written Communication Skills
- Collaboration and Teamwork

Soft Skills:

- Time Management
- Adaptability and Learning Agility

Cybersecurity:

- Basic Understanding of Cybersecurity Principles
- Best Practices for Secure Coding

UI/UX Design:

- Wireframing and Prototyping
- User-Centric Design Principles

Languages:

Fluent in English and Filipino

EXPERIENCE

2023-2024 Full time Student, edX x University of Toronto, Ontario

Full-stack web development bootcamp

2020-2022 Full time Student, University of the Philippines, Diliman, Quezon City

• Graduated with a Bachelor of Science degree in Architecture.

2020-2021 Account Manager, RCEF Extension Program

- Managed and coordinated interviewee schedules against the film team and interviewer's availability.
- Served as the conduit between the company and the interviewees for any changes or cancellations to the plans.
- Ensured proper logistical execution of on-the-day live streams and pre-recorded episodes of weekly web TV shows.

2017-2020 Owner, FAT Fries and Toppings

- Conceptualized and executed on creating an establishment that would serve delicious and reasonably priced food.
- Developed and tested recipes that would cater to the widest possible palate.
- Managed and trained employees in proper food handling, customer service, and report generation.

2012-2017 Campaign Manager, Wideout Workforces, Inc./Cognizant Technology Solutions, Inc.

- Developed and maintained professional relationships with clients through email and phone
- Assisted with the execution of Google Rich Media campaigns, including planning, launching, monitoring, analyzing, and communicating effective and ineffective areas of the campaign to
- Managed, troubleshot, and resolved issues with clients' Google Rich Media Campaigns.
- Effectively maintained client expectations and consistently met key deadlines by staying connected through email and phone communication.

2007-2012 Professional Photographer

Sponsored and recognized by Nikon as one of the top photographers in the country.

- Held seminars on both studio and natural lighting in multiple countries such as Kuwait, Guam, and the Philippines.
- Shot multiple covers for magazines such as Illustrado Magazine Dubai, Cook Magazine, and Ad Lib.
- Shot for Robinsons Land ad campaigns, which appeared on billboards as well as print ads.
- Regularly covered events for MTV, FHM, and Maxim.

2009-2010 Art Director, The Design People

- Managed up to sixty clients simultaneously.
- Conceptualized, executed, and presented website designs, keeping in mind the clients' preferences and ideal sites.
- Worked closely with web designers and developers to execute the planned designs.

2005-2008 General Manager, The Chocolate Kiss Café

- Set yearly sales and profit targets with the board of directors.
- Reviewed daily, monthly, and yearly expenditures.
- Provided and executed on the vision, mission, and daily goals of the establishment.
- Managed relationships with external vendors and business clients.

2003-2005 Assistant Team Leader, iTouchPoint

- Managed escalated calls from agents and resolved client complaints.
- Evaluated agents against the KPIs that the organization has set.
- Coached agents on improving their AHT and CSAT scores.
- Achieved fourteen straight weeks of 100% QA scores.

Education

University of the Philippines College of Architecture

- Bachelor of Science in Architecture
- Chairperson of U.P. Architecture Forum (student organization)
- Externals Committee Head, U.P. Architecture Forum

https://www.linkedin.com/in/indra-levi-manahan-908912154/